Andrew Eichinger

Front-end developer and musician with a passion for creating enriched web experiences. With almost a decade of experience in songwriting and production, I approach each project through a creative lens to build user-friendly, responsive, and accessible web applications.

Toronto, ON 647-614-4403

andreweichinger21@gmail.com andreweichinger.com linkedin

SKILLS

HTML5





React

jQuery

CSS3







Firebase







EDUCATION

Juno College

Web Development Bootcamp Intro to Web Development / JavaScript 2021

University of Western Ontario

Bachelor of Arts - Film 2010 - 2013

WORK HISTORY

Q4 Inc. | Web Developer I

Nov 2021 - Aug 2022

- Built and updated investor relations websites for various clients
- Used SCSS to style templates based on figma designs and HTML, jQuery, Javascript to build modules for custom projects
- Worked with widgets powered by public and private CMS content API's to render collections of financial data, documents and content using Javascript templating engines
- Collaboration with other developers to optimize templates and widgets
- Example | Example

Freelance Web Developer

July 2021

 Built and designed responsive multi-page website for local construction company using HTML/SCSS/JavaScript

Songwriter, Touring Musician, Owner

2013 - Present

- Songwriting, production, and creative direction responsibilities on four full length albums
- Creative director on album artwork, music videos, merchandise, and social marketing
- Consultation with record labels and management on the successful deployment of albums, tour promotions, and brand initiatives

PROJECTS

Daily Crypto Updates | Javascript | API | SCSS

Live Site | GitHub

Is The Book Better? | React | API

Live Site | GitHub